

- (305) 582-2466
- Eronegirl@gmail.com

About Me

An junior graphic designer yearning to pass along creative ideas to others. Two years of experience in graphic design, including a full-time role as a student. Focusing on continuing education and professional training.

Skills

Logo Design / Branding
Brochure Design / Layout
Color Management / Photo
Manipulation
Poster Design
Photography
Catalogue Layout
Logo Animation

Graphic Design

Estela Riquelme

Education

Bachelor's in Fine Arts

2016 - Current

Miami International University of Art and Design

High School Diploma

2012 - 2016

Hialeah-Miami Lakes Senior High

Experience

Call Service Agent

2018 - Current

Inktel - Goodyear

To utilize our knowledge of the company's products, services, and policies to assist callers with inquiries, complaints, or problems. To speak with customers, listen to them to gain a better understanding of their needs, and offer possible solutions.

Breakfast Buffet Attendant

2018 - 2018

Kimpton Angler's Hotel

To provide a clean dining area, bussing tables in an efficient, courteous and accurate manner. All functions are carried out to maintain an environment of teamwork.

Technology Student Worker

2017 - 2018

Miami International University

Helps customers with print projects, and equipment rentals. Helps give a positive environment for customers and employees. Manages computer software and maintaining excellent condition for printers.